export const GroupQuestion = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  REQUEST_UPDATE_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'REQUEST_UPDATE_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  FAIL_REQUEST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  GET_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'GET_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  UPDATE_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'UPDATE_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  POST_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION: 'POST_LIST_GROUP_QUESTION',
  POST_REPORT: 'POST_REPORT',
  CLEAR_LIST_ANSWER_REPORT: 'CLEAR_LIST_ANSWER_REPORT',
}

export const IQTest = {
  UPDATE_LIST_ANSWER: 'UPDATE_LIST_ANSWER',
  POST_ANSWER: 'POST_ANSWER',
  REQUEST_POST_ANSWER: 'REQUEST_POST_ANSWER',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_ANSWER: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_ANSWER',
  CLEAR_LIST_ANSWER: 'CLEAR_LIST_ANSWER',
}

export const Report = {
  FAIL_REQUEST_REPORT: 'FAIL_REQUEST_REPORT',
  REQUEST_POST_REPORT: 'REQUEST_POST_REPORT',
  POST_REPORT: 'POST_REPORT',
  REQUEST_GET_REPORT: 'REQUEST_GET_REPORT',
  GET_REPORT: 'GET_REPORT',
}

export const Auth = {
  FAIL_REQUEST_AUTH: 'FAIL_REQUEST_AUTH',
  REQUEST_AUTH_LOGIN: 'REQUEST_LOGIN',
  AUTH_LOGIN: 'AUTH_LOGIN',
  AUTH_LOGOUT: 'AUTH_LOGOUT',
  REQUEST_BUSINESS_LOGIN: 'REQUEST_BUSINESS_LOGIN',
  BUSINESS_LOGIN: 'BUSINESS_LOGIN',
  BUSINESS_LOGOUT: 'BUSINESS_LOGOUT',
  REQUEST_BUSINESS_RESET_PASSWORD: 'REQUEST_BUSINESS_RESET_PASSWORD',
  BUSINESS_RESET_PASSWORD: 'BUSINESS_RESET_PASSWORD',
  FAIL_REQUEST_BUSINESS_PASSWORD: 'FAIL_REQUEST_BUSINESS_PASSWORD',
}

export const Profile = {
  FAIL_REQUEST_PROFILE: 'FAIL_REQUEST_PROFILE',
  REQUEST_GET_PROFILE: 'REQUEST_GET_PROFILE',
  GET_PROFILE: 'GET_PROFILE',
  UPDATE_PROFILE_INFORMATION: 'UPDATE_PROFILE_INFORMATION',
  UPDATE_PROFILE_INFORMATION_SUCCESS: 'UPDATE_PROFILE_INFORMATION_SUCCESS',
  CHECKOUT_PAYMENT: 'CHECKOUT_PAYMENT',
  REQUEST_PUT_FB_PROFILE: 'REQUEST_PUT_FB_PROFILE',
  PUT_FB_PROFILE: 'PUT_FB_PROFILE',
  REQUEST_PUT_PROFILE: 'REQUEST_PUT_PROFILE',
  PUT_PROFILE: 'PUT_PROFILE',
  UPDATE_FB_PROFILE: 'UPDATE_FB_PROFILE',
}

export const Transaction = {
  FAIL_REQUEST_TRANSACTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_TRANSACTION',
  REQUEST_CHECKOUT_PAYMENT: 'REQUEST_CHECKOUT_PAYMENT',
  CHECKOUT_PAYMENT: 'CHECKOUT_PAYMENT',
}

export const ModalError = {
  OPEN_MODAL_ERROR: 'OPEN_MODAL_ERROR',
  CLOSE_MODAL_ERROR: 'CLOSE_MODAL_ERROR',
}

export const ModalTimedOut = {
  OPEN_MODAL_TIMED_OUT: 'OPEN_MODAL_TIMED_OUT',
  CLOSE_MODAL_TIMED_OUT: 'CLOSE_MODAL_TIMED_OUT',
}

export const Blog = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_BLOG: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_BLOG',
  GET_LIST_BLOG: 'GET_LIST_BLOG',
  FAIL_REQUEST_BLOG: 'FAIL_REQUEST_BLOG',
}

export const Statistics = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_STATISTICS: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_STATISTICS',
  GET_LIST_STATISTICS: 'GET_LIST_STATISTICS',
  FAIL_REQUEST_STATISTICS: 'FAIL_REQUEST_STATISTICS',
}

export const Dashboard = {
  GET_LIST_CANDIDATE: 'GET_LIST_CANDIDATE',
  GET_LIST_CANDIDATE_SUCCESS: 'GET_LIST_CANDIDATE_SUCCESS',
  GET_LIST_CANDIDATE_FAILED: 'GET_LIST_CANDI_FAILEDDATE',
  GET_LIST_POSITION: 'GET_LIST_POSITION',
  GET_LIST_POSITION_SUCCESS: 'GET_LIST_POSITION_SUCCESS',
  GET_LIST_POSITION_FAILED: 'GET_LIST_POSITION_FAILED',
  GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE: 'GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE',
  GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE_SUCCESS: 'GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE_SUCCESS',
  GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE_FAILED: 'GET_NUMBER_OF_CANDIDATE_FAILED',
  SET_FILTERS: 'SET_FILTERS',
  SET_PROFILE: 'SET_PROFILE',
  GET_PROFILE_PATTERNS: 'GET_PROFILE_PATTERNS',
  REQUEST_CHANGE_PASSWORD: 'REQUEST_CHANGE_PASSWORD',
  CHANGE_PASSWORD: 'CHANGE_PASSWORD',
  FAIL_REQUEST_CHANGE_PASSWORD: 'FAIL_REQUEST_CHANGE_PASSWORD',
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH',
  GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH: 'GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH',
  FAIL_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH: 'FAIL_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_MONTH',
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK',
  GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK: 'GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK',
  FAIL_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK: 'FAIL_GET_LIST_EVENT_BY_WEEK',
  ADD_TEMPORARY_EVENT: 'ADD_TEMPORARY_EVENT',
  REMOVE_TEMPORARY_EVENT: 'REMOVE_TEMPORARY_EVENT',
  REQUEST_POST_CV: 'REQUEST_POST_CV',
  POST_CV: 'POST_CV',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_CV: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_CV',
  CLEAR_CV: 'CLEAR_CV',
  REQUEST_GET_CV: 'REQUEST_GET_CV',
  GET_CV: 'GET_CV',
  FAIL_REQUEST_GET_CV: 'FAIL_REQUEST_GET_CV',
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_CV: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_CV',
  GET_LIST_CV: 'GET_LIST_CV',
  FAIL_REQUEST_GET_LIST_CV: 'FAIL_REQUEST_GET_LIST_CV',
}

export const LRBrainQuestion = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION',
  GET_LIST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION: 'GET_LIST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION',
  FAIL_REQUEST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_LR_BRAIN_QUESTION',
  UPDATE_LIST_LR_BRAIN_ANSWER: 'UPDATE_LIST_LR_BRAIN_ANSWER',
  REQUEST_POST_BRAIN_ANSWER: 'REQUEST_POST_BRAIN_ANSWER',
  POST_ANSWER: 'POST_ANSWER',
  CLEAR_LIST_BRAIN_ANSWER: 'CLEAR_LIST_BRAIN_ANSWER',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_BRAIN_ANSWER: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_BRAIN_ANSWER',
}

export const EQQuestion = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_EQ_QUESTION: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_EQ_QUESTION',
  GET_LIST_EQ_QUESTION: 'GET_LIST_EQ_QUESTION',
  FAIL_REQUEST_EQ_QUESTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_EQ_QUESTION',
  UPDATE_LIST_EQ_ANSWER: 'UPDATE_LIST_EQ_ANSWER',
  POST_EQ_ANSWER: 'POST_EQ_ANSWER',
  REQUEST_POST_EQ_ANSWER: 'REQUEST_POST_EQ_ANSWER',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_EQ_ANSWER: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_EQ_ANSWER',
  CLEAR_LIST_EQ_ANSWER: 'CLEAR_LIST_EQ_ANSWER',
}

export const CustomTestQuestion = {
  REQUEST_GET_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION: 'REQUEST_GET_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION',
  GET_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION: 'GET_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION',
  FAIL_REQUEST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_CUSTOM_TEST_QUESTION',
  UPDATE_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER: 'UPDATE_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER',
  POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER: 'POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER',
  REQUEST_POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER: 'REQUEST_POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER',
  CLEAR_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER: 'CLEAR_LIST_CUSTOM_TEST_ANSWER',
}

export const SingleChoiceQuestion = {
  GET_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_QUESTION: 'GET_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_QUESTION',
  FAIL_REQUEST_SINGLE_CHOICE_QUESTION: 'FAIL_REQUEST_SINGLE_CHOICE_QUESTION',
  UPDATE_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER: 'UPDATE_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER',
  POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER: 'POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER',
  REQUEST_POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER: 'REQUEST_POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER',
  FAIL_REQUEST_POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER: 'FAIL_REQUEST_POST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER',
  CLEAR_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER: 'CLEAR_LIST_SINGLE_CHOICE_ANSWER',
}

export const BusinessProfile = {
  FAIL_REQUEST_BUSINESS_PROFILE: 'FAIL_REQUEST_BUSINESS_PROFILE',
  REQUEST_GET_BUSINESS_PROFILE: 'REQUEST_GET_BUSINESS_PROFILE',
  GET_BUSINESS_PROFILE: 'GET_BUSINESS_PROFILE',
  REQUEST_PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN: 'REQUEST_PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN',
  PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN: 'PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN',
  FAIL_REQUEST_PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN: 'FAIL_REQUEST_PUT_BUSINESS_FIRST_LOGIN',
}
